myvisajobs.com 2007-12-26

# Privacy Policy::MyVisaJobs.Com

**M** **yVisaJobs.com** **Privacy Policy**

Thank you for visiting myvisajobs.com. This Privacy Policy details certain policies implemented throughout myvisajobs.com governing myVisaJobs.com's use of personally identifiable information provided to myVisaJobs.com via this Site or otherwise.

**Privacy Policy Updates**

Due to the Internet's rapidly evolving nature, myVisaJobs.com may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, myVisaJobs.com will post its updated Privacy Policy on our Site located at www.myVisaJobs.com and may send you an email so you are always aware of what personally identifiable information we may collect and how we may use this information. myVisaJobs.com encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this Site will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy.

**Information Collection and Use**

You can generally visit our Site without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. However, in certain sections of this Site, to use certain services, we may require you to create an account, or we may invite you to submit questions or comments or request information, subscribe to a newsletter, participate in surveys, questionnaires or contests, or message boards. Due to the nature of some of these activities, we may ask that you complete and submit an online form with personally identifiable information such as your name, username, email address, zip code and contact information. If you have created an account, you may opt to provide additional personally identifiable information in your profile such as your age, gender and employment information. Providing any additional personally identifiable information beyond what is required to create an account is optional. We may use your personally identifiable information to deliver certain services, products or information you have requested, verify your authority to enter certain password protected areas of the Site, send you notices for services that you have used or that may be of interest to you, and improve the content and general administration of the Site. We may receive your personally identifiable information from our partners that provide us with third-party services so that we can customize and improve the services that we may provide to you. Additionally, if you have elected to reveal your email address to other registered members, they will have access to and be able to use your email address.

**Children's Privacy**

myVisaJobs.com is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. myVisaJobs.com 's services and Site are not intended for and may not be used by children under the age of 13. myVisaJobs.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 and myVisaJobs.com does not target its services or this Site to children under 13.

**Cookies**

We may use small text files called cookies to improve overall Site experience. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you. Some advertisements that appear on this Site are delivered to you by our advertising partners. Our advertising partners may download cookies to your computer. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement. In this way, they may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. This information allows an advertising network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. We do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers.

**Aggregate Information**

The Site may track the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, IP addresses, External Web Sites (defined below) linked to, search terms and the domain names of our users' Internet Service Providers, and we may analyze these data for trends and statistics in the aggregate, but such information will be maintained, used and disclosed in aggregate form only and it will not contain personally identifiable information. We also may collect aggregate labor statistics from public records. Such aggregate information is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We may use such aggregate information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may share this aggregate information with third parties, including for various reasons related to our business to assist them in targeting advertisements to appropriate audiences.

**Disclosure**

We may disclose your personally identifiable information and aggregate information to our partner entities that provide job networking services to us to improve the content and general administration of our Site. Any such partner entity to which we provide your personally identifiable information may not further distribute your personally identifiable information.

We will also disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to any other company or organization except we may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which Simply Hired participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of Simply Hired’s assets to which this Site relates. Such successor entity shall be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

**Links to Third Party Sites**

The Site may provide links to other Web sites or resources over which myVisaJobs.com does not have control ("External Web Sites"). Such links do not constitute an endorsement by myVisaJobs.com of those External Web Sites. You acknowledge that myVisaJobs.com is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that myVisaJobs.com is not responsible for the content of such External Web Sites. Your use of External Web Sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked to External Web Sites.

**Security**

We may employ procedural and technological measures, consistent with industry practice. Such measures are reasonably designed to help protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. myVisaJobs.com may use firewalls, internal restrictions, password protection, physical lock and key and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information.

**Correction/Updating Personally Identifiable Information**

myVisaJobs.com provides you with the ability to review, correct and delete any of the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us. If you wish to review or correct any information you have provided to us, you may access your account and review, correct and delete your personally identifiable information.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us.
